这些非常昂贵 我知道他很快就穿不下…
These were expensive and he'll grow out of them...
但是我就是无法抗拒！
...in 20 minutes,but I couldn't resist!
看看这些！
Look at these.
嗨，班
Hey,Ben.
做了就对！ （耐克广告词）
"Just do it"!
喔，天啊！
Oh,my God!
是不是对他压力太大？
Was that too much pressure for him?
他已经饿了吗？ 我想是的
-ls he hungry already? -I guess so.
你知道，那个…
You know,it's....
球鞋真的很有趣 我马上就回来！
Something funny about sneakers. I'll be right back.
我也要一个
I gotta get one too.
你们在干什么？
Hey,what are you guys doing?
我们只是来看看汤匙
We're just hanging out by the spoons.
要调羹吗？
Ladle?
你们成熟一点好吗？
Will you guys grow up?
这是世上最自然美丽的
This is the most beautiful thing in the world.
我们知道 但现在有个婴儿在吸它
Yeah,we know. But there's a baby sucking on it.
这是我儿子在吃午餐 你们最好习惯
This is my son having lunch,okay? It'll happen a lot,so get used to it.
如果你们感到不自在 发问就好
If you're uncomfortable,just ask questions.
卡萝不介意的
Carol's fine with it.
卡萝？
Carol?
我想问问乔伊能不能提出 关于哺乳的问题？
I'm wondering,could Joey ask you a question about breast-feeding?
当然可以
Sure.
会不会痛？
Does it hurt?
刚开始会，现在不会了
It did at first,but not anymore.
钱德？
Chandler?
你能多久喂一次？
So,how often can you do it?
只要他需要就可以
As much as he needs.
我想到了一个问题
Okay,I got one,I got one.
如果他对一个吹气 另一个会不会变大？
If he blows into one,does the other one get bigger?
The One With the Breast Milk
六人行 第2季 第02集 母乳
还有松糕吗？ 还有，我忘记还有哪一种
-Any muffins left? -Yeah,I forget which ones.
你太忙了，我来拿
You're busy,I'll get it.
谁还要？ 不用，谢谢
-Anyone else want one? -No,thanks.
你的围裙松了，我帮你系好
You're losing your apron. Let me get it.
好了 谢谢
-There you go. -Thank you.
婊子！
What a bitch!
我有朋友在布鲁明戴尔百货上班 明天就不干了
I have a friend at Bloomingdale's who's quitting...
他想要花掉他的折扣券
...and he wants to abuse his discount.
谁想跟我去捡便宜？
Anyone want to come take advantage of it?
我不行 我要带我祖母去看兽医
I have to take my grandmother to the vet.
我跟你去 好极了
-I'll go with you. -Great.
嗨，甜心 嗨，蜜糖
-Hi,honey. -Hey,sweetums.
嗨，其余的各位
And hello to the rest.
你不能跟她去逛百货 瑞秋怎么办？
You can't go shopping with her. What about Rachel?
会有问题，对不对？
Will it be a problem?
你要跟茱莉去布鲁明戴尔
You're going to Bloomingdale's with Julie.
就像是到瑞秋家中偷男人！
It's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship.
她会宰了你
Monica,she will kill you.
她会宰了你 就像宰街上的流浪狗！
She will kill you like a dog in the street!
茱莉说你们明天要去逛街
So Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow.
其实没有什么…
It's actually not that big a deal.
对我很重要，非常重要
It's a big deal to me. This is great.
我非常感激你这么做
I really appreciate this.
别客气
You're welcome.
毕坚男士香水？（世界十大昂贵香水之一）
Bijan for men?
毕坚男士香水？
嗨，安娜贝 嗨，乔伊
-Hey,Annabel. -Hey,Joey.
听说过新来的人吗？
Did you hear about the new guy?
没人知道他的名字 我们女生都叫他“西班牙男人”
Nobody knows his name. Me and the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
西班牙男人？
Hombre?
他到我这一区干什么？
What's he doing in my section?
我想他不知道
I guess he doesn't know.
他必须知道
Well,he's gonna.
待会见
I'll see you a little later,okay?
你好吗？
Hey,how you doing?
早
Mornin'.
听着，我知道你是新来的…
Listen,I know you're new...
但众所皆知这附近的一切…
... but it's understood that everything...
从年轻人部门到电梯… 都是我的地盘
...from young men's to the escalator is my territory.
你的地盘？
"Your territory"?
毕坚男士香水？ 不，谢了
-Bijan for men? -No,thanks.
西班牙男人？
Hombre?
好啊
Yeah,all right.
你刚才说什么？
You were saying?
菲比，听着，你跟我一起 逛了整天街买东西
Phoebe,listen. You were with me,and we were shopping all day.
我们买东西，吃午餐
We shopped and we had lunch.
我吃了什么？
What did I have?
你吃了沙拉 难怪我不饱
-You had a salad. -No wonder I don't feel full.
嗨，怎么样？
Hi. What's up?
我整天都跟莫妮卡买东西 吃了一客沙拉
I went shopping with Monica and I had a salad.
很好，菲比 你们买了什么？
Good,Pheebs. What'd you buy?
我们去买了…
We went shopping for....
嗯…
For....
买了皮草
For fur.
你去买皮草？
You went shopping for fur?
然后我发现我反对买皮草
And then I realized that l'm against that.
于是我们买了一些…
So then we bought some....
波霸
Boobs.
你买了波霸？
You bought boobs?
胸罩！
Bras!
我们买了胸罩！
We bought bras!
我们买了胸罩
We bought bras.
毕坚男士香水？
Bijan for men?
毕坚…
Bijan for....
嗨，安娜贝
Hey,Annabel.
下班后我们可以喝个咖啡吗？
I was wondering if after work we could grab a cup of coffee?
我已经有计划了
Actually,I sort of have plans.
准备好了吗，安娜贝？
You ready,Annabel?
好了
You bet.
以后再约吧
Maybe some other time.
这又不是第一次被喷香水的牛仔抢走女友
It's not the first time I lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne.
毕坚男士香水？
Bijan for men?
毕坚男士香水！
Bijan for men!
这是滑稽小丑
And this is Funny Clown.
只有睡过午觉才可以给他玩 否则他不会睡
It's only for after his naps,not before,or he won't sleep.
我带过他，我们玩得很高兴
We've been through this before. We have a good time.
我们又笑又玩 就像父亲跟儿子一样
We laugh,we play. It's like we're father and son.
亲爱的，放轻松 罗斯很会带他
Honey,relax. Ross is great with him.
别这么惊讶 我是个很好的人
Don't look so surprised. I'm a lovely person.
好可爱！
This is so cute!
我为他买的！
I got that for him!
“我的妈妈们爱我”
"My Mommies Love Me. "
真聪明
That's clever.
嗨，茱…
Oh,hi,Jul....
嗨，犹太人！
Hi,Jew!
好的，可以
Okay,sure.
很好，待会见
That'd be great. See you then. Bye.
你刚才是不是说： 嗨，犹太人？
Did you just say," Hi,Jew"?
对，我是这么说
Yes,I did.
那是我的犹太朋友 艾迪莫斯考维兹
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
他全都是这样的宗教事情
He's going through this whole religious thing.
他很喜欢这称呼 能加强他的信仰
Yeah,he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
班，吃晚餐了！
Ben,dinner!
谢谢，菲比姑妈
Thanks,Aunt Pheebs.
你没有用微波炉吧？ 不应该这样处理母乳
Did you microwave that? You can't do that to breast milk.
我想我知道如何加热母乳
I think I know how to heat breast milk.
你在干什么？
What did you just do?
我舔了我的手臂，怎么样？
I licked my arm,what?
那是母乳！
It's breast milk!
又怎么样？
So?
菲比 那是从另一个人身上挤出的汁
Phoebe,that is juice squeezed from a person.
有什么了不起？
What is the big deal?
你又在干什么？
What did you just do?
大家能不能不要喝母乳？
Can people stop drinking the breast milk?
你连尝都不尝？
You won't even taste it?
不能假装那是牛奶吗？
Not even if you just pretend it's milk?
就算卡萝的乳房 帖了牛奶寻人广告都不行！
Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.
大家到哪里去了？ 带班去公园了，你去哪里了？
-Where is everybody? -At the park. Where have you been?
出去
Just out.
吃了午餐，只有我一个人 与自己共度美好时光
Had some lunch. Just me. A little quality time with me.
谢谢你的外套 别客气
-Thanks for your jacket. -No problem.
你也可以向我借
You can borrow it,by the way.
这是你的钥匙
Here are your keys,honey.
如果你一个人吃午餐 怎么会要五十三块？
If you were at lunch alone,how come it cost you $53?
你知道大概发生什么事吗？
You know what probably happened?
一定有人偷了我的信用卡
Someone stole my credit card.
然后把收据放回你口袋？
And put the receipt back in your pocket?
这是个非常好的问题
That is an excellent,excellent question.
真的非常好
That is excellent.
你怎么了？ 跟谁吃午餐？
What's with you? Who did you have lunch with?
茱蒂 谁？
-Judy. -Who?
茱莉 什么？
-Julie. -What?
裘迪
Jody.
你跟茱莉在一起？
You were with Julie?
刚开始我只是想对她友善点…
When it started,I was just trying to be nice to her...
因为她是我哥哥的女友
... because she was my brother's girlfriend.
然后事情接着发生…
And then one thing led to another...
我还不清楚，我们就…
...and before I knew it,we were...
去购物了
...shopping.
我的天！
Oh,my God!
慢着，我们只做了一次
Wait,we only did it once.
对我没有任何意义！
It meant nothing to me!
我一直想的是你！
Really,I was thinking of you the whole time.
对不起，好吗？ 我不希望你知道的
Look,I'm sorry,all right? I never meant for you to find out.
拜托！你希望被逮到！
Oh,please! Please! You wanted to get caught!
才不是！
That is not true!
所以你不小心留收据在这里？
So you just happened to leave it in here?
你有没有想到 我会这么笨？
Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
好，我必须知道一件事
Okay,I just have to know one thing.
你是不是跟她去布鲁明戴尔？
Did you go to Bloomingdale's?
我现在不能跟你在一起了
Okay,I just really need to not be with you right now.
嗨，哪一位？
Hi,who's this?
嗨，琼安，瑞秋在吗？ 我是莫妮卡
Hi,Joanne. Is Rachel working? It's Monica.
我知道我做了很糟糕的事
Yes,I know I did a horrible thing.
琼安，事情没这么简单
Joanne,it's not as simple as all that.
我才不在乎史提夫怎么想 嗨，史提夫
No,I don't care what Steve thinks. Hi,Steve.
情况如何？
How did we do?
我尝了班的奶水 罗斯发癫了
I tasted Ben's milk and Ross freaked out.
我没有发癫
I did not freak out.
你为什么发癫？ 因为那是母乳
-Why'd you freak out? -Because it's breast milk.
很恶心！
It's gross!
我的奶水很恶心？
My breast milk is gross?
这会很好玩
This should be fun.
这没什么不对
There's nothing wrong with it.
我只是不认为 母乳是给大人喝的
I just don't think breast milk is for adults.
当然母乳的容器 很吸引大人与小孩
Of course,the packaging does appeal to grownups and kids.
别傻了，我试过，没什么
Don't be silly. I've tried it. It's no big deal.
尝一尝
Just taste it.
不行
That would be no.
来嘛 尝一尝
-Come on. -Try it.
很自然
It's natural.
又不难吃
It doesn't taste bad.
有一点甜，很像…
Yeah,it tastes kind of sweet. Sort of like....
像什么？
Like what?
哈密瓜汁
Cantaloupe juice.
没错
Exactly.
你尝过了
You've tasted it.
喔，你尝过了
Oh,you've tasted it.
你可以一直说下去 也不会变成假话
You can keep saying it,but it won't stop being true.
把奶瓶给我
Give me the bottle.
把毛巾给我
Get me the towel.
你好（方言，不常用）
Howdy.
给我一罐果汁
Give me a box of juice.
他们把我调到“西班牙男人”了
Well,they switched me over to Hombre.
也许是因为你的穿着
Maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.
或因为那砘锉硐痔好了 他们要增加人手
Or this guy's doing so good they want to put more people on it.
那砘镆惶煊玫袅狡
This guy goes through two bottles a day now.
你在乎什么？
What do you care?
你是个演员 这只是你的副业，没什么
You're an actor. This is your day job. It's nothing!
我知道，但我本来是最棒的
I know,but I was the best.
我喜欢当最棒的
You know? I liked being the best.
也许我应该退出这场游戏
Maybe I should get out of the game.
厨具部门需要有人切乳酪
They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.
假如你这么做了
Say you do that.
将来迟早有人会出现 乳酪切得比你更好
Sooner or later,somebody will come along that slices a better cheddar.
那时候你要逃到哪里？
Then where you gonna run?
也许你说得对
You're right.
我说你应该发挥大丈夫气概
I say you show him what you're made of. Stand your ground.
让他知道你是内衣部西边最厉害的西班牙男人！
Show him that you're the baddest Hombre west of the lingerie!
我要这么做！ 好极了
-I'm gonna do it! -All right!
现在去找猫咪小姐 她会介绍个好妓女给你
Now,go see Miss Kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
很好，因为我不会听
That's good because I'm not listening.
我觉得很糟糕，真的
I feel terrible. I really do.
对不起 我的背伤害了你的刀吗？
I'm sorry. Did my back hurt your knife?
我跟她交朋友，一起去逛街 这有什么不好？
Say that I'm friends with her. Is that so terrible?
真的很不好吗？ 是的，你还不懂吗？
-It's that terrible? -You don't get it!
她偷走我的男人已经够糟了…
It's bad enough she stole the guy...
我可能会跟他长相厮守
...who may be the person l'm supposed to be with.
但现在…
But now...
她竟然…
...she's actually....
现在她竟然连你也抢走了！
But now she's actually stealing you!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
没人能把我从你那里抢走
Nobody could steal me from you.
我与她交朋友 不会影响我与你的感情
Because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you.
你是我的…
You're my....
我们是…
And we're....
喔，我爱你！ 我也爱你！
-Oh,I love you! -I love you too!
喂，我知道这与我完全无关
You guys,I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me.
但我也爱你们！
But I love you guys too!
我很需要这样
I really needed that.
我知道现在…
I know that right now...
你很想恨死茱莉
...you really need to hate Julie's guts.
但她没有做什么错事
But she didn't do anything wrong.
她只是认识了一个男生 现在他们在交往
She's just a girl who met a guy,and now they go out.
我想如果你给她一个机会 你会喜欢她的
I think that if you gave her a chance,you'd like her.
你愿意给她一个机会吗？
Will you give it a chance?
为了我？
For me?
我愿意为你做任何事 你知道的
I'd do anything for you,you know that.
我什么都愿意为你做！
I'd do anything for you!
等一下！
Wait,wait,wait!
早
Mornin'.
我说：早！
I said,mornin'!
我听见了
I heard you.
好，各位 我要开门了
All right,everybody. I'm opening the doors.
你们准备好了吗？
You boys ready?
好了
Ready.
我也好了
Yeah,l'm ready.
你这个白痴！ 笨牛仔！
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
你弄瞎我了！我要告你们！
You've blinded me! I'm suing!
天啊！陶德！你在搞什么鬼！
Oh,my God! Todd! What the hell did you do?
对不起，我真是笨手笨脚！
Sorry. I'm such a doofus!
对不起，非常对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
老天，发生什么事？
My God,what happened?
这些菜鸟，都撑不了很久
These new kids,they never last.
迟早他们就会…
Sooner or later they all...
…止步前进
...stop lasting.
我们去喝杯咖啡怎么样？
What do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
好啊
Sure.
我想我们应该亲近亲近
I just thought we should hang out.
你知道的 我们从来没有真正谈过话
I mean,you know,we've never really talked.
你知道的 因为你是我们两个之一
I guess you'd know that,being one of the two of us.
我知道
I know.
我也许不该告诉你…
I probably shouldn't even tell you this...
但我实在很怕你
... but l'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.
真的？
Really?
怕我？
Me?
你在开玩笑吗？
Oh,my God,are you kidding?
罗斯还是对你很着迷…
Ross is so crazy about you...
我真的希望你喜欢我
...and I really wanted you to like me,and l....
也许我只是胡思乱想…
It's probably me just being totally paranoid...
但我好像觉得你不喜欢我
...but I kind of got the feeling that maybe you don't.
你不是完全胡思乱想
Well,you're not totally paranoid.
当你与罗斯刚开始交往时…
When you and Ross first started going out...
我真的很难过…
...it was really hard for me...
有太多理由，我不能给你造成困扰
...for many reasons of which l'm not gonna bore you with now.
但我看到他非常快乐 而且你们在一起是多么相配
I see how happy he is and how good you guys are together.
莫妮卡一直说你有多好…
And Monica's always saying how nice you are...
真讨厌她说得对！
...and God,I hate it when she's right!
谢谢
Thanks.
你想不想一起去看电影 或出去玩？
Would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
这样很好，我很乐意
Yeah,that'd be great. I'd love it.
我也是
I'd love it too.
我必须要走了
Shoot,I gotta go.
待会见 好，茱莉
-So I'll talk to you later. -All right,Julie.
真是个玩弄人的贱人！
What a manipulative bitch.
真不赖
It's not bad.